Guide to the William Marsh Rice business and estate ledgers, 1855-1965 UA 102
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Business and Estate Ledgers
  - Ledger B; Rice Ranch; includes separate index, 1896-1898 (Box 54, Item 85)
  - Administration and budget - Restricted, 1939-1940 (Box 55)
  - Departments - Restricted, 1939-1940 (Box 55)
  - Administration and budget - Restricted, 1948-1949 (Box 55)
  - Departments - Restricted, 1948-1949 (Box 55)
  - Administration and budget - Restricted, 1949-1950 (Box 55)
  - Bursar - Restricted, 1949-1950 (Box 55)
  - Departments - Restricted, 1949-1950 (Box 55)
  - Administration - Restricted, 1957-1966 (Box 55)
  - Departments - Restricted, 1961-1966 (Box 55)
  - Student Affairs and Colleges - Restricted, 1957-1966 (Box 55)
  - Cash Book B-1; Rice Institute, July 1907-Nov. 1911 (Box 56, Item 107)
  - Cash Book B-2; Rice Institute, Dec. 1911-Feb. 1913 (Box 57, Item 112)
  - Cash Book B-3; Rice Institute, March-May 1913 (Box 58, Item 113)